Rick Whitesell Record Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 3. 7" Discs, 3; 12 linear feet Boxes: 1 - 23 Folders: 3.7.1 - 3.7.1883
  - The Moonglows, Record Label:Oldies (Folder 1404, Box 18)
    - Real Gone Mama, 1
    - Secret Love, 2
  - The Moonglows, Record Label:Times Square (Folder 1405, Box 18)
    - Baby Please, 1
    - I've Got The Right, 2
  - The Moroccos, Record Label:Ember (Folder 1406, Box 18)
    - What Is A Teen-Ager's Prayer, 1
    - Bang Goes My Heart, 2
  - Billy Myles, Record Label:Ember (Folder 1407, Box 18)
    - Honey Bee, 1
    - The Joker (That's What They Call Me), 2
  - The Mystics, Record Label:Laurie (Folder 1408, Box 18)
    - So Tenderly, 1
    - Don't Take The Stars, 2
  - The Mystics, Record Label:Laurie (Folder 1409, Box 18)
    - Adam And Eve, 1
    - Hushabye, 2
  - The Native Boys, Record Label:Combo (Folder 1410, Box 18)
    - Strange Love, 1
    - Cheerlyn, 2
  - The Native Boys, Record Label:Combo (Folder 1411, Box 18)
    - Laughing Love, 1
    - Valley Of Lovers, 2
  - Nazz, Record Label:SGC (Folder 1412, Box 18)
    - Open My Eyes, 1
    - Hello, It's Me, 2
  - The Neons, Record Label:Vintage (Folder 1413, Box 18)
    - Honey Bun, 1
    - Golden Dreams, 2
  - Nickey&The Nobles, Record Label:Gone (Folder 1414, Box 18)
    - School Day Crush, 1
    - School Bells, 2
  - Nino&The Ebb Tides, Record Label:Madison (Folder 1415, Box 18)
    - Don't Run Away, 1
    - Those Oldies But Goodies (Remind Me Of You), 2
  - Nino&The Ebb Tides, Record Label:Madison (Folder 1416, Box 18)
    - (Someday) I'll Fall In Love, 1
    - Juke Box Saturday Night - featuring “Book Of Love” and “Get A Job”, 2
  - The Nitecaps, Record Label:Groove (Folder 1417, Box 18)
    - By My Girl, 1
    - A Kiss And A Vow, 2
  - Jimmy Norman, Record Label:Samar (Folder 1418, Box 18)
    - Can You Blame Me, 1
    - This I Beg Of You, 2
  - The Nuggets, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 1419, Box 18)
    - Shtiggy Boom, 1
    - Anxious Heart, 2
  - The Nutmegs, Record Label:Herald (Folder 1420, Box 18)
    - Comin' Home, 1
    - A Love So True, 2
  - The Nutmegs, Record Label:Herald (Folder 1421, Box 18)
    - Story Untold, 1
    - Make Me Lose My Mind, 2
  - The Nutmegs, Record Label:Herald (Folder 1422, Box 18)
    - Rock Me, 1
    - Ship Of Fools, 2
  - The Nutmegs, Record Label:Lana (Folder 1423, Box 18)
    - Ship Of Love, 1
    - Tingaling, 2
  - The Nutmegs, Record Label:Lana (Folder 1424, Box 18)
    - Beautiful Dreamer, 1
    - Story Untold, 2
  - The Olympics, Record Label:Arvee (Folder 1425, Box 18)
    - Dooley, 1
    - Stay Where You Are, 2
  - The Olympics, Record Label:Demon (Folder 1426, Box 18)
    - Well!, 1
    - Western Movies, 2
  - The Orioles, Record Label:Jubilee (Folder 1427, Box 18)
    - At Night, 1
    - Every Dog-Gone Time, 2
  - The Orioles, Record Label:Jubilee (Folder 1428, Box 18)
    - In The Chapel In The Moonlight, 1
    - Thank The Lord! Thank The Lord!, 2
  - The Orioles, Record Label:Jubilee (Folder 1429, Box 18)
    - What Are You Doing New Year's Eve, 1
    - (It's Gonna Be A) Lonely Christmas, 2
  - The Orlandos, Record Label:Cindy (Folder 1430, Box 18)
    - Cloudburst, 1
    - Old MacDonald, 2
  - The Johnny Otis Show, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 1431, Box 18)
    - Willie And The Hand Jive, 1
    - Ring-A-Ling, 2
  - The Paradons, Record Label:Milestone (Folder 1432, Box 18)
    - Please Tell Me, 1
    - Bells Ring, 2
  - The Paradons, Record Label:Milestone (Folder 1433, Box 18)
    - I Want Love, 1
    - Diamond And Pearls, 2
  - The Paragons, Record Label:Winley (Folder 1434, Box 18)
    - Just A Memory, 1
    - Kneel And Pray, 2
  - The Paragons, Record Label:Winley (Folder 1435, Box 18)
    - Hey Little School Girl, 1
    - Florence, 2
  - The Paragons, Record Label:2 Copies Winley (Folder 1436, Box 18)
    - Stick With Me Baby, 1
    - Let's Start All Over Again, 2
  - The Passions, Record Label:Audicon (Folder 1437, Box 18)
    - Gloria, 1
    - Jungle Drums, 2
  - The Passions, Record Label:Audicon (Folder 1438, Box 18)
    - I Only Want You, 1
    - This Is My Love, 2
  - The Passions, Record Label:Audicon (Folder 1439, Box 18)
    - Oh Melancholy Me, 1
    - Just To Be With You, 2
  - The Passions, Record Label:Audicon (Folder 1440, Box 18)
    - Beautiful Dreamer, 1
    - One Look Is All It Took, 2
  - The Pastels, Record Label:Argo (Folder 1441, Box 18)
    - My One And Only Dream, 1
    - Been So Long, 2
  - Patience And Prudence, Record Label:Liberty (Folder 1442, Box 18)
    - Gonna Get Along Without Ya Now, 1
    - Tonight You Belong To Me, 2
  - Bobby Patterson And The Mustangs, Record Label:Jetstar (Folder 1443, Box 18)
    - Sock Some Lovin' At Me, 1
    - I'm Leroy - I'll Take Her, 2
  - Les Paul And Mary Ford, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 1444, Box 18)
    - Goodbye, My Love, 1
    - Hummingbird, 2
  - The Pearls, Record Label:Onyx (Folder 1445, Box 18)
    - Zippidy Zippidy Zoom, 1
    - Let's You And I Go Steady, 2
  - The Penguins, Record Label:Dooto (Folder 1446, Box 18)
    - Love Will Make Your Mind Go Wild, 1
    - Ookey Ook, 2
  - The Penguins, Record Label:Dootone (Folder 1447, Box 18)
    - Earth Angel, 1
    - Hey Senorita, 2
  - The Penguins, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1448, Box 18)
    - Earth Angel, 1
    - Ice, 2
  - The Penguins, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1449, Box 18)
    - Don't Do It, 1
    - Be Mine Or Be A Fool, 2
  - The Penguins, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1450, Box 18)
    - Walkin' Down Broadway, 1
    - It Only Happens With You, 2
  - The Persuaders, Record Label:Winley (Folder 1451, Box 18)
    - Tears, 1
    - What Could It Be?, 2
  - The Pharaos, Record Label:Donna (Folder 1452, Box 18)
    - The Tender Touch, 1
    - Heads Up, High Hopes Over You, 2
  - The Philharmonics, Record Label:Future (Folder 1453, Box 18)
    - Why Don't You Write Me?, 1
    - Teen Town Hop, 2
  - Esther Phillips, Record Label:Atlantic (Folder 1454, Box 18)
    - Makin' Whoopee, 1
    - Moonglow&Theme From Picnic, 2
  - Phil Phillips, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1455, Box 18)
    - Juella, 1
    - Sea Of Love, 2
  - The Pilgrim Jubilee Singers, Record Label:Peacock (Folder 1456, Box 18)
    - Turn You 'Round, 1
    - Pearly Gates, 2
  - The Plants, Record Label:J&S (Folder 1457, Box 18)
    - It's You, 1
    - Dear I Swear, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1458, Box 18)
    - Tell The World, 1
    - I Need You All The Time, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1459, Box 18)
    - The Great Pretender, 1
    - I'm Just A Dancing Partner, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1460, Box 18)
    - It Isn't Right, 1
    - You'll Never Never Know, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1461, Box 18)
    - Smoke Gets In Your Eyes, 1
    - No Matter What You Are, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1462, Box 18)
    - Twilight Time, 1
    - Out Of My Mind, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1463, Box 18)
    - Ebb Tide, 1
    - (I'll Be With You In) Apple Blossom Time, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1464, Box 18)
    - Bark, Battle And Ball, 1
    - Only You (And You Alone), 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1465, Box 18)
    - To Each His Own, 1
    - Down The River Of Golden Dreams, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1466, Box 18)
    - The Sound And The Fury, 1
    - Enchanted, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1467, Box 18)
    - You Don't Say, 1
    - I'll Never Smile Again, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1468, Box 18)
    - My Old Flame, 1
    - You're Making A Mistake, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1469, Box 18)
    - Indiff'rent, 1
    - Helpless, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1470, Box 18)
    - I'm Sorry, 1
    - He's Mine, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1471, Box 18)
    - Immortal Love, 1
    - Trees, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1472, Box 18)
    - One In A Million, 1
    - On My Word Of Honor, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1473, Box 18)
    - Heaven On Earth, 1
    - My Prayer, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1474, Box 18)
    - I Wanna, 1
    - My Dream, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Mercury (1475, Box 19)
    - Winner Take All, 1
    - (You've Got) The Magic Touch, 2
  - The Platters, Record Label:Musicor (Folder 1476, Box 19)
    - The Magic Touch, 1
    - I'll Be Home, 2
  - The Playmates, Record Label:Savoy (Folder 1477, Box 19)
    - Giddy-Up-A-Ding-Dong, 1
    - It Must Be Love, 2
  - Earl Plummer, Record Label:East West (Folder 1478, Box 19)
    - Two Loves Have I, 1
    - Give Me Your Love, 2
  - The Plurals, Record Label:Bergen (Folder 1479, Box 19)
    - Miss Annie, 1
    - Donna My Dear, 2
  - The Plurals, Record Label:Wanger (Folder 1480, Box 19)
    - Goodnight, 1
    - I'm Sold, 2
  - Jesse Powell Orchestra, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1481, Box 19)
    - Love Is A Fortune, 1
    - The Walkin' Blues (Walk Right In, Walk Right Out), 2
  - Elvis Presley, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1482, Box 19)
    - I'm Yours, 1
    - (It's A) Long Lonely Highway, 2
  - Elvis Presley, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1483, Box 19)
    - His Latest Flame, 1
    - Little Sister, 2
  - Elvis Presley, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1484, Box 19)
    - Good Rockin' Tonight, 1
    - I Don't Care If The Sun Don't Shine, 2
  - Elvis Presley, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1485, Box 19)
    - Too Much, 1
    - Playing For Keeps, 2
  - Elvis Presley, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1486, Box 19)
    - All Shook Up, 1
    - That's When Your Heartaches Begin, 2
  - Elvis Presley, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1487, Box 19)
    - One Broken Heart For Sale, 1
    - They Remind Me Too Much Of You, 2
  - Elvis Presley, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1488, Box 19)
    - Cradle Of Love, 1
    - City Of Tears, 2
  - Elvis Presley, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1489, Box 19)
    - Rip It Up, 1
    - Love Me, 2
    - When My Blue Moon Turns To Gold Again, 3
    - Paralyzed, 4
  - Elvis Presley, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1490, Box 19)
    - Don't Be Cruel, 1
    - I Want You, I Need You, I Love You, 2
    - Hound Dog, 3
    - My Baby Left Me, 4
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (Folder 1491, Box 19)
  - Johnny Preston, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1492, Box 19)
    - Cradle Of Love, 1
    - City Of Tears, 2
  - The Pretenders, Record Label:Bethlehem (Folder 1493, Box 19)
    - The Day You Are Mine, 1
    - Ding Dong Bells, 2
  - The Pretenders, Record Label:Rama (Folder 1494, Box 19)
    - I've Got To Have You Baby, 1
    - Possessive Love, 2
  - The Pretenders, Record Label:Relic (Folder 1495, Box 19)
    - Smile, 1
    - I'm So Happy, 2
  - Lloyd Prince And His Orchestra, Record Label:ABC Paramount (Folder 1496, Box 19)
    - Just Because, 1
    - Why, 2
  - Lloyd Prince And His Orchestra, Record Label:ABC Paramount (Folder 1497, Box 19)
    - Personality, 1
    - Have You Ever Had The Blues, 2
  - Lloyd Prince, Record Label:Specialty (Folder 1498, Box 19)
    - Lawdy Miss Clawdy, 1
    - Mailman Blues, 2
  - Lloyd Prince, Record Label:Specialty (Folder 1499, Box 19)
    - Breaking My Heart, 1
    - Baby, Please Come Home, 2
  - The Prisonaires, Record Label:Sun (Folder 1500, Box 19)
    - I Know, 1
    - A Prisoner's Prayer, 2
  - The Prisonaires, Record Label:Sun (Folder 1501, Box 19)
    - Baby Please, 1
    - Just Walkin' In The Rain, 2
  - The Prisonaires, Record Label:Sun (Folder 1502, Box 19)
    - My God Is Real, 1
    - Softly And Tenderly, 2
  - Arthur Prysock, Record Label:Wing (Folder 1503, Box 19)
    - Come Home, 1
    - Woke Up This Morning, 2
  - Red Prysock, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1504, Box 19)
    - Jumbo, 1
    - Hand Clappin', 2
  - Red Prysock, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1505, Box 19)
    - Hand Clappin', 1
    - Shoe String, 2
  - Red Prysock, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1506, Box 19)
    - Zonked, 1
    - The Horn Blows, 2
  - Red Prysock, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1507, Box 19)
    - Blow Your Horn, 1
    - Happy Feet, 2
  - Red Prysock, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1508, Box 19)
    - Rock 'N Roll, 1
    - Little Jamie, 2
  - The Pyramids, Record Label:Shell (Folder 1509, Box 19)
    - Ankle Bracelet, 1
    - Hot God Dooly Wah, 2
  - The Quails, Record Label:Harvey (Folder 1510, Box 19)
    - My Love, 1
    - Never Felt Like This Before, 2
  - The Quarter Notes, Record Label:Wizz (Folder 1511, Box 19)
    - Suki-Yaki-Rocki, 1
    - Record Hop Blues, 2
  - The Quin-Tones, Record Label:Hunt (Folder 1512, Box 19)
    - Please Dear, 1
    - Down The Aisle Of Love, 2
  - The Quin-Tones, Record Label:Hunt (Folder 1513, Box 19)
    - What Am I To Do, 1
    - There'll Be No Sorrow, 2
  - The Quin-Tones, Record Label:Red Top (Folder 1514, Box 19)
    - Oh, Heavenly Father, 1
    - I Watch The Stars, 2
  - The Quotations, Record Label:Verve (Folder 1515, Box 19)
    - Imagination, 1
    - Ali-Men-Sy, 2
  - The Rainbows, Record Label:Red Robin (Folder 1516, Box 19)
    - Mary Lee, 1
    - Evening, 2
  - The Ravels, Record Label:Vee-Jay (Folder 1517, Box 19)
    - Lonely One, 1
    - Shombalor, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:Argo (Folder 1518, Box 19)
    - Water Boy, 1
    - A Simple Prayer, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:Argo (Folder 1519, Box 19)
    - Lazy Mule, 1
    - Here Is My Heart, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:2 Copies Argo (Folder 1520, Box 19)
    - Dear One, 1
    - That'll Be The Day, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:Jubilee (Folder 1521, Box 19)
    - We'll Raise A Ruckus Tonight, 1
    - On Chapel Hill, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:Jubilee (Folder 1522, Box 19)
    - Green Eyes, 1
    - The Bells Of San Raquel, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:Jubilee (Folder 1523, Box 19)
    - Happy Go Lucky Baby, 1
    - Bye Bye Baby Blues, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:Mercury (Folder 1524, Box 19)
    - Rock Me All Night Long, 1
    - Write Me One Sweet Letter, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:National (Folder 1525, Box 19)
    - Count Every Star, 1
    - It's The Talk Of The Town, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:Savoy (Folder 1526, Box 19)
    - Silent Night, 1
    - White Christmas, 2
  - The Ravens, Record Label:Song Masters EP (Folder 1527, Box 19)
    - Without A Song, 1
    - Would You Believe Me, 2
    - Write Me A Letter, 3
    - Careless Love, 4
  - The Ravens, Record Label:Top Rank (Folder 1528, Box 19)
    - The Rising Sun, 1
    - Into The Shadows, 2
  - The Rays, Record Label:Cameo (Folder 1529, Box 19)
    - Daddy Cool, 1
    - Silhouettes, 2
  - The Rays, Record Label:Cameo (Folder 1530, Box 19)
    - Rags To Riches, 1
    - The Man Above, 2
  - The Rays, Record Label:XYZ (Folder 1531, Box 19)
    - Louie Hoo Hoo, 1
    - Magic Moon, 2
  - The Rays, Record Label:XYZ (Folder 1532, Box 19)
    - Zimba Lulu, 1
    - Why Do You Look The Other Way?, 2
  - Red Buttons, Record Label:Columbia (Folder 1533, Box 19)
    - The Ho Ho Song, 1
    - Strange Things Are Happening, 2
  - The Regents, Record Label:Gee (Folder 1534, Box 19)
    - Runaround, 1
    - Laura My Darling, 2
  - The Regents, Record Label:Gee (Folder 1535, Box 19)
    - Barbara-Ann, 1
    - I'm So Lonely, 2
  - The Regents, Record Label:Gee (Folder 1536, Box 19)
    - Liar, 1
    - Don't Be A Fool, 2
  - Willie Restum, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 1537, Box 19)
    - Restum In Peace Blues, 1
    - One-Note Boogie, 2
  - Willie Restum, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 1538, Box 19)
    - Rock-A-Beatin' Boogie, 1
    - What'd He Say, 2
  - The Revalons, Record Label:Pet (Folder 1539, Box 19)
    - This Is The Moment, 1
    - Dreams Are For Fools, 2
  - The Revels, Record Label:Norgolde (Folder 1540, Box 19)
    - Midnight Stroll, 1
    - Talking To My Heart, 2
  - Rudi Richardson, Record Label:Sun (Folder 1541, Box 19)
    - Why Should I Cry, 1
    - Fool’s Hall Of Fame, 2
  - Jimmy Ricks, Record Label:Felsted (Folder 1542, Box 19)
    - Secret Love, 1
    - If It Didn't Hurt So Much, 2
  - Jimmy Ricks, Record Label:Felsted (Folder 1543, Box 19)
    - Leaning On Your Love, 1
    - Here Come The Tears Again, 2
  - Jimmy Ricks, Record Label:Signature (Folder 1544, Box 19)
    - At Sunrise, 1
    - Goodnight My Love, 2
  - Jimmy Ricks&The Ravens, Record Label:Jubilee (Folder 1545, Box 19)
    - (Take Me Back To My) Boots And Saddles, 1
    - I'll Always Be In Love With You, 2
  - Jimmy Ricks&His Rickateers, Record Label:Josie (Folder 1546, Box 19)
    - She's Fine - She's Mine, 1
    - The Unbeliever, 2
  - Tom Ridgely, Record Label:Herald (Folder 1547, Box 19)
    - When I Meet My Girl, 1
    - What'cha Gonna Do, 2
  - The Rivieras, Record Label:Coed (2 copies) (Folder 1548, Box 19)
    - True Love Is Hard To Find, 1
    - Count Every Star, 2
  - The Rivieras, Record Label:Coed (Folder 1549, Box 19)
    - 11th Hour Melody, 1
    - Since I Made You Cry, 2
  - The Rivieras, Record Label:Coed (Folder 1550, Box 19)
    - Moonlight Serenade, 1
    - Neither Rain Nor Snow, 2
  - The Rivieras, Record Label:Coed (Folder 1551, Box 19)
    - Blessing Of Love, 1
    - Moonlight Cocktails, 2
  - The Rivieras, Record Label:Coed (Folder 1552, Box 19)
    - Easy To Remember, 1
    - Stay In My Heart, 2
  - The Rivileers, Record Label:Baton (Folder 1553, Box 19)
    - Who Is The Girl, 1
    - A Thousand Stars, 2
  - Robert&Johnny, Record Label:Old Town (Folder 1554, Box 19)
    - Old Town, 1
    - I Believe In You, 2
  - Robert&Johnny, Record Label:Old Town (Folder 1555, Box 19)
    - I Believe In You, 1
    - Train To Paradise, 2
  - Robert&Johnny, Record Label:Old Town (Folder 1556, Box 19)
    - Oh My Love, 1
    - Dream Girl, 2
  - Robert&Johnny, Record Label:Old Town (Folder 1557, Box 19)
    - Walking In The Rain, 1
    - We Belong Together, 2
  - Robert&Johnny, Record Label:Old Town (Folder 1558, Box 19)
    - Eternity With You, 1
    - I'm Truly Truly Yours, 2
  - The Robins, Record Label:RCA Victor (1559, Box 20)
    - Let's Go To The Dance, 1
    - How Would You Know, 2
  - The Robins, Record Label:Spark (Folder 1560, Box 20)
    - Whadaya Want?, 1
    - If Teardrops Were Kisses, 2
  - Rochell&The Candles, Record Label:Swingin' (Folder 1561, Box 20)
    - So Far Away, 1
    - Hey, Pretty Baby, 2
  - Rochell&The Candles, Record Label:Swingin' (Folder 1562, Box 20)
    - Once Upon A Time, 1
    - When My Baby Is Gone, 2
  - The Rolling Stones, Record Label:Atlantic (Folder 1563, Box 20)
    - Dancing With Mr. D, 1
    - Doo Doo Doo Doo Doo (Heartbreaker), 2
  - The Romans, Record Label:Del-Fi (Folder 1564, Box 20)
    - Those Oldies But Goodies, 1
    - She Don't Wanna Dance, 2
  - The Ronnetes, Record Label:Philles (Folder 1565, Box 20)
    - Tedesco and Pitman, 1
    - Be My Baby, 2
  - Ronnie&The Hi-Lites, Record Label:Joy (Folder 1566, Box 20)
    - Be Kind, 1
    - Send My Love (Special Delivery), 2
  - Ronnie&The Hi-Lites, Record Label:Joy (Folder 1567, Box 20)
    - Twistin' And Kissin', 1
    - I Wish That We Were Married, 2
  - The Roomates, Record Label:Valmor (Folder 1568, Box 20)
    - O Baby Love, 1
    - Band Of Gold, 2
  - The Royal Holidays, Record Label:Carlton (Folder 1569, Box 20)
    - Margaret, 1
    - I'm Sorry (I Did You Wrong), 2
  - The Royals, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1570, Box 20)
    - I Feel So Blue, 1
    - The Shrine Of St. Cecelia, 2
  - The Royals, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1571, Box 20)
    - Get It, 1
    - No It Ain't, 2
  - The Royals, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1572, Box 20)
    - Moonrise, 1
    - Fifth Street Blues, 2
  - The Royals, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1573, Box 20)
    - A Love In My Heart, 1
    - I'll Never Let Her Go, 2
  - The Royals, Record Label:Federal (Folder 1574, Box 20)
    - What Did I Do, 1
    - Are You Forgetting, 2
  - The Royal Teens, Record Label:Capitol (Folder 1575, Box 20)
    - Believe Me, 1
    - Little Cricket, 2
  - The Royaltones, Record Label:Old Town (Folder 1576, Box 20)
    - Crazy Love, 1
    - Never Let Me Go, 2
  - Willis Sanders&The Embers, Record Label:Unart (Folder 1577, Box 20)
    - Honey-Bun, 1
    - Lovable You, 2
  - The Satins, Record Label:Ember (Folder 1578, Box 20)
    - A Night To Remember, 1
    - Senorita Lolita, 2
  - The Scarlets, Record Label:Event (Folder 1579, Box 20)
    - I've Lost, 1
    - Dear One, 2
  - The Scarlets, Record Label:Fury (Folder 1580, Box 20)
    - Truly Yours, 1
    - East Of The Sun, 2
  - The Schoolboys, Record Label:OKeh (Folder 1581, Box 20)
    - Shirley, 1
    - Please Say You Want Me, 2
  - Jack Scott, Record Label:Top Rank (Folder 1582, Box 20)
    - Baby, Baby, 1
    - What In The World's Come Over You, 2
  - Jack Scott, Record Label:Top Rank (Folder 1583, Box 20)
    - Cool Water, 1
    - It Only Happened Yesterday, 2
  - Jack Scott, Record Label:Top Rank (Folder 1584, Box 20)
    - Burning Bridges, 1
  - Neil Sedaka, Record Label:RCA Victor (Folder 1585, Box 20)
    - Oh! Carol, 1
    - One Way Ticket, 2
  - The Sensations, Record Label:Argo (Folder 1586, Box 20)
    - Let Me In, 1
    - Oh Yes, I'll Be True, 2
  - The Sensations, Record Label:Argo (Folder 1587, Box 20)
    - A Part Of Me, 1
    - Music, Music, Music, 2
  - The Sensations, Record Label:Atco (Folder 1588, Box 20)
    - You Made Me Love You, 1
    - My Debut To Love, 2
  - The Sensations, Record Label:Atco (Folder 1589, Box 20)
    - Yes Sir, That's My Baby, 1
    - Sympathy, 2
  - The Sedates, Record Label:Twentieth Century (Folder 1590, Box 20)
    - Please Love Me Forever, 1
    - I Found, 2
  - The Sharps, Record Label:Lamp (Folder 1591, Box 20)
    - Lock My Heart, 1
    - Our Love Is Here To Stay, 2
  - The Shells, Record Label:Johnson (Folder 1592, Box 20)
    - Happy Holiday, 1
    - Deep In My Heart, 2
  - The Shells, Record Label:Johnson (Folder 1593, Box 20)
    - Pleading No More, 1
    - Don't Say Goodbye, 2
  - The Shells, Record Label:Johnson (Folder 1594, Box 20)
    - Baby Oh Baby, 1
    - What's In An Angel's Eyes, 2
  - Shep&The Limelites, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1595, Box 20)
    - In Case I Forget, 1
    - I'm A Hurting Inside, 2
  - Shep&The Limelites, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1596, Box 20)
    - Oh, What A Feeling, 1
    - Three Steps From The Altar, 2
  - Shep&The Limelites, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1597, Box 20)
    - Our Anniversary, 1
    - Who Told The Sandman, 2
  - Shep&The Limelites, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1598, Box 20)
    - I'm All Alone, 1
    - Why Did You Fall For Me, 2
  - Shep&The Limelites, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1599, Box 20)
    - Teach Me, Teach Me How To Twist, 1
    - What Did Daddy Do, 2
  - Shep&The Limelites, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1600, Box 20)
    - Daddy's Home, 1
    - This I Know, 2
  - Shep&The Limelites, Record Label:Hull (Folder 1601, Box 20)
    - You'll Be Sorry, 1
    - Ready For Your Love, 2
  - Buddy Sheppard, Record Label:Sabina (Folder 1602, Box 20)
    - Time To Dream, 1
    - My Love Is Real, 2
  - The Sheppards, Record Label:Abner (Folder 1603, Box 20)
    - Loving You, 1
    - Elevator Operator, 2
  - The Sheppards, Record Label:Apex (Folder 1604, Box 20)
    - Island Of Love, 1
    - Never Felt This Way Before, 2
  - The Sheppards, Record Label:Apex (Folder 1605, Box 20)
    - Tragic, 1
    - Feel Like Lovin, 2
  - The Sheppards, Record Label:Apex (Folder 1606, Box 20)
    - It's Crazy, 1
    - Meant To Be, 2
  - The Shields, Record Label:Dot (Folder 1607, Box 20)
    - Nature Boy, 1
    - I'm Sorry Now, 2
  - intentionally skipped, Record Label: (Folder 1608, Box 20)
  - The Shirelles, Record Label:Scepter (Folder 1609, Box 20)
    - Mama Said, 1
    - Blue Holiday, 2
  - The Shirelles, Record Label:Scepter (Folder 1610, Box 20)
    - Soldier Boy, 1
    - (Mama) My Soldier Boy Is Coming Home, 2
  - The Shirelles, Record Label:Scepter (Folder 1611, Box 20)
    - Dedicated To The One I Love, 1
    - Look A Here Baby, 2
  - The Shirelles, Record Label:Scepter (Folder 1612, Box 20)